[Music]
You all know what road
safety means.
What is this?
This Safe India
Foundation has
surveyed six or seven schools here regarding road safety
and has suggested
how to establish safety zones there. I
welcome it. This is such a work,
such a Himalayan task, which
needs the cooperation of all of you. We have done more than 1.5 lakh road safety surveys for all of India. The
main point of this is that if children are
educated, they can become smart.
How can we take them forward in their homes? When their
parents
go ahead without helmets and they see them, they will have
helmets. They can
tell them further that helmets are important. Safety is very
important. It is not just a helmet, it is the
difference between life and death.
I have faced this on a personal level when I was a student.
Wearing a helmet
saved my life. Helmet is
not a complete safety zone, it is the difference between life and death.
And there is an
insurance company, so there is another safety that
you all need.  Is it necessary to stay at home or children should
ask in their homes, they are adults, they should
ask themselves
when
you are
in a bad time, sometimes
fighting between life and death, then when someone
dies, then you have only
one companion, only one friend
and the
third party
insurance is done by the government
and it is very important that
you people go to your homes, those who have bikes or vehicles in their homes,
go and ask in their homes whether it
is insured, if it is not insured then get it done,
this security should be there in both ways, there is
security of the body before life
and after life, if there is insurance then insurance
which is very important